How it fits, usually to
accelerate your work. Um, you cannot use
it as evidence because if you know how
AI works,
it's not evidence of real
user behavior.
Um, but you can
experiment with different experiment
types so that it gives you ideas.
Uh, you don't need to look a lot for
ideas that are easy and so on. It can
give you tons of it. You can define the
hypothesis that you can test. You can
generate, I don't know, landing page
copy or do a ton of landing pages or ads
or stuff.
And you can brainstorm a lot on test
variations and what you should focus and
so on for that mine,
minimum viable experiment.
You shouldn't use AI to decide if your
idea works, so skip the experiments, do
the experiments with AI.
You shouldn't skip running it
ever. So, people are still,
people, companies are heavily doing this
anyhow and it doesn't replace real user
behavior.